Black Sparrow Press Collection, 1966-1994 (bulk 1973-1993)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series I: Book Files, 1973-1993
  - #345 Proud Beggars by Albert Cossery translated by Cushing, Thomas, First Manuscript (Discarded Materials), 1981 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - #345 Proud Beggars by Albert Cossery translated by Cushing, Thomas, Original Manuscript in French, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - #345 Proud Beggars by Albert Cossery translated by Cushing, Thomas, Final Manuscript, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - #345 Proud Beggars by Albert Cossery translated by Cushing, Thomas,1 Hardcover Copy, 1 Softcover, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - #345 Proud Beggars by Albert Cossery translated by Cushing, Thomas, 2 Hardcover Copy, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - #346 Selected Poems 1958-1980, Sorrentino, Gilbert, Artwork, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - #346 Selected Poems 1958-1980, Sorrentino, Gilbert, Manuscript, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - #346 Selected Poems 1958-1980, Sorrentino, Gilbert, 1 Hardcover Copy, 3 Softcover, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - #346 Selected Poems 1958-1980, Sorrentino, Gilbert, 2 Hardcover Copy, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - #347 Midnight Mass, Bowles, Paul, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - #347 Midnight Mass, Bowles, Paul, Manuscript, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - #347 Midnight Mass, Bowles, Paul, Artwork, Unbound Copy, First Proof, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - #347 Midnight Mass, Bowles, Paul, 3 Hardcover copy, 2 Softcover, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - #348 Next to Nothing, Collected Poems 1926-1977, Bowles, Paul, Artwork, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - #348 Next to Nothing, Collected Poems 1926-1977, Bowles, Paul, Manuscript, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - #348 Next to Nothing, Collected Poems 1926-1977, Bowles, Paul, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - #349 The Apes of God, Lewis, Wyndham, Artwork, Negatives, Ephemera, Correspondence, Notes, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - #349 The Apes of God, Lewis, Wyndham, 2 First Trade Editions (1930) Hardcover Copies, 1 Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - #349 The Apes of God, Lewis, Wyndham, 4 Hardcover copies, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - #350 Thrice Chosen, Roditi, Edouard, Correspondence, Notes, Artwork, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - #350 Thrice Chosen, Roditi, Edouard, First Draft (Discarded Materials), 1981 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - #350 Thrice Chosen, Roditi, Edouard, Manuscript, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - #351 Dangling in the Tournefortia, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - #351 Dangling in the Tournefortia, Bukowski, Charles, First Draft, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - #351 Dangling in the Tournefortia, Bukowski, Charles, Manuscript, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - #351 Dangling in the Tournefortia, Bukowski, Charles, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - #352 Spiritual Exercises Kelly, Robert, Correspondence, Notes, Review, Artwork, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - #352 Spiritual Exercises Kelly, Robert, Manuscript, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - #352 Spiritual Exercises Kelly, Robert, 2 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - #353 Blast 1, Lewis, Wyndham, Correspondence, Notes, Artwork, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - #353 Blast 1, Lewis, Wyndham, 2 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - #354 Blast 2, Lewis, Wyndham, Notes, Review, Artwork, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - #354 Blast 2, Lewis, Wyndham, 1 Softcover, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - #354 Blast 2, Lewis, Wyndham, 2 Hardcover copies, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - #355 Complete Correspondence #3, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Correspondence, Notes, Review, Artwork, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - #355 Complete Correspondence #3, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Manuscript, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover; 1981 (Box 85, Folder 3, Folder 4)
  - #356 Dreams from Bunker Hill, Fante, John, Correspondence, Notes, Review, Artwork, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - #356 Dreams from Bunker Hill, Fante, John, Manuscript, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - #356 Dreams from Bunker Hill, Fante, John, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - #357 A Man Without Shoes, Sanford, John, Correspondence, Reviews, First Introduction, Artwork, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - #357 A Man Without Shoes, Sanford, John, Correspondence, 1 Hardcover copy, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - #358 The Last Generation, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - #358 The Last Generation, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, 2 Softcover copies, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - #358 The Last Generation, Bukowski, Charles, 2 Hardcover copies, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - #359 Complete Correspondence #4, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Correspondence, Notes, Artwork, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - #359 Complete Correspondence #4, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Manuscript, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - #359 Complete Correspondence #4, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, 3 Hardcover copies, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - #360 Musician’s Feastletters, Wakoski, Diane, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, Artwork, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - #360 Musician’s Feastletters, Wakoski, Diane, First Manuscript (Discarded Materials), 1982 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - #360 Musician’s Feastletters, Wakoski, Diane, Second Manuscript, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - #360 Musician’s Feastletters, Wakoski, Diane, Proof, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - #360 Musician’s Feastletters, Wakoski, Diane, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - #361 Birth of a Poet,, Everson, William, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, Artwork, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - #361 Birth of a Poet, Everson, William, Manuscript, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - #361 Birth of a Poet, Everson, William, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - #362 The Spider’s House, Bowles, Paul, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, Artwork, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - 362 The Spider’s House, Bowles, Paul, 2 Hardcover original copies with notes, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - #362 The Spider’s House, Bowles, Paul, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - #363 A More Goodly Country, Sanford, John, Reviews, Artwork, Manuscript, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - #363 A More Goodly Country, Sanford, John, Reviews, 1 Hardcover copy, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - #364 The Formal Voice, Shelnutt, Eve, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, Artwork, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - #364 The Formal Voice, Shelnutt, Eve, First Manuscript (Discarded Materials), 1982 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - #364 The Formal Voice, Shelnutt, Eve, Second Manuscript, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - #364 The Formal Voice, Shelnutt, Eve, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - #365 Ham on Rye, Bukoski, Charles, Correspondence, Reviews, Notes, Artwork, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - #365 Ham on Rye, Bukoski, Charles, First Manuscript, 15 folders, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - #365 Ham on Rye, Bukoski, Charles, First Manuscript, 15 folders, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - #365 Ham on Rye, Bukoski, Charles, Second Draft, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - #365 Ham on Rye, Bukoski, Charles,Third Draft, pg 1-199, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - #365 Ham on Rye, Bukoski, Charles, Third Draft, pg 200-386, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - #365 Ham on Rye, Bukoski, Charles, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - #365 Ham on Rye, Bukoski, Charles, 1 Hardcover copy, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - #366 The Complete Wild Body, Lewis, Wyndham, Correspondence, Reviews, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - #366 The Complete Wild Body, Lewis, Wyndham, Artwork, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - #366 The Complete Wild Body, Lewis, Wyndham, First Draft (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - #366 The Complete Wild Body, Lewis, Wyndham, First Draft (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - #366 The Complete Wild Body, Lewis, Wyndham, First Manuscript (Discarded Materials), 1982 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - #366 The Complete Wild Body, Lewis, Wyndham, Second Manuscript, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - #366 The Complete Wild Body, Lewis, Wyndham, First Proofs, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - #366 The Complete Wild Body, Lewis, Wyndham, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - #367 The Plain of Smokes, Mudd, Harvey and Price, Ken, Correspondence, Reviews, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - #367 The Plain of Smokes, Mudd, Harvey and Price, Ken, Slides, Artwork, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - #367 The Plain of Smokes, Mudd, Harvey and Price, Ken, Manuscript, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - #367 The Plain of Smokes, Mudd, Harvey and Price, Ken, First Proofs, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - #367 The Plain of Smokes, Mudd, Harvey and Price, Ken, Second Proof, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - #367 The Plain of Smokes, Mudd, Harvey and Price, Ken, Third Proof, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - #367 The Plain of Smokes Mudd, Harvey and Price, Ken, Unbound copy, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - #367 The Plain of Smokes, Mudd, Harvey and Price, Ken, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - #368 Krazy Kat and 76 More, Dawson, Fielding, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - #368 Krazy Kat and 76 More, Dawson, Fielding, Artwork, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - #368 Krazy Kat and 76 More, Dawson, Fielding, Manuscript, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - #368 Krazy Kat and 76 More, Dawson, Fielding, 1 Softcover copy, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - #369 Horsemeat, Bukowski, Charles, 3 Hardcover, 1 Softcover, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - #369 Horsemeat, Bukowski, Charles, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - #369 Horsemeat, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - #369 Horsemeat, Bukowski, Charles, First Manuscript, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - #369 Horsemeat, Bukowski, Charles, Second Manuscript, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - #369 Horsemeat, Bukowski, Charles, Proof, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - #370 Journey into Barbary, Lewis, Wyndham, Correspondence, Notes, Notice, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - #370 Journey into Barbary, Lewis, Wyndham, Artwork (illustration negatives), 1982 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - #370 Journey into Barbary, Lewis, Wyndham, Manuscript (boxed), 1982 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - #370 Journey into Barbary, Lewis, Wyndham, Second Proof, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - #370 Journey into Barbary, Lewis, Wyndham, 3 Hardcover copies,1 Softcover, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - #371 Sparks, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - #371 Sparks, Bukowski, Charles, 3 Unbound copies, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - #371 Sparks, Bukowski, Charles, 1 Hardcover copy, 2 Softcover, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - #372 Wait Until Spring, Bandini, Fante, John, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, 1983 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - #372 Wait Until Spring, Bandini, Fante, John, Artwork, 1983 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - #372 Wait Until Spring, Bandini, Fante, John, Artwork, 1 Hardbound copy (original with new and deleted material), 1983 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - #372 Wait Until Spring, Bandini, Fante, John, Proof, 1983 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - #372 Wait Until Spring, Bandini, Fante, John, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1983 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - #373 Complete Correspondence #5, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Correspondence, Notes, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - #373 Complete Correspondence #5, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Correspondence, Artwork, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - #373 Complete Correspondence #5, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, Manuscript, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - #373 Complete Correspondence #5, Olson, Charles and Creeley, First Proof, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - #373 Complete Correspondence #5, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Second Proof, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - #373 Complete Correspondence #5, Olson, Charles and Creeley, Robert, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - #374 Waters/Places/A Time, Eigner, Larry, Correspondence, Notes, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - #374 Waters/Places/A Time, Eigner, Larry, Artwork, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - #374 Waters/Places/A Time, Eigner, Larry, Manuscript, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - #374 Waters/Places/A Time, Eigner, Larry, 2 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - #375 Self Condemned, Lewis, Wyndham, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - #375 Self Condemned, Lewis, Wyndham, Artwork, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - #375 Self Condemned, Lewis, Wyndham, Third Proof, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - #375 Self Condemned, Lewis, Wyndham, New Material to be Set, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - #375 Self Condemned, Lewis, Wyndham, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - #376 Fracture, Eshleman, Clayton, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - #376 Fracture, Eshleman, Clayton, Artwork (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - #376 Fracture, Eshleman, Clayton, Manuscript, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - #376 Fracture, Eshleman, Clayton, First Proof, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - #376 Fracture, Eshleman, Clayton, Second Proof, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - #376 Fracture, Eshleman, Clayton, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - #377 This Will Kill That, Malanga, Gerard, Correspondence, Notes, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - #377 This Will Kill That, Malanga, Gerard, Artwork (pictures), 1983 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - #377 This Will Kill That, Malanga, Gerard, First Manuscript (Discarded Materials), 1983 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - #377 This Will Kill That, Malanga, Gerard, Final Manuscript, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - #377 This Will Kill That, Malanga, Gerard, 2 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - #378 Bring Me Your Love, Bukowski, Charles and Crumb, R., Original Manuscript, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - #378 Bring Me Your Love, Bukowski, Charles and Crumb, R., Final Manuscript, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - #378 Bring Me Your Love, Bukowski, Charles and Crumb, R., Proofs (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - #378 Bring Me Your Love, Bukowski, Charles and Crumb, R. Artwork, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - #379 The Unexamined Wife, Jaffe, Sherril, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - #379 The Unexamined Wife, Jaffe, Sherril, Artwork, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - #379 The Unexamined Wife, Jaffe, Sherril, Second Proof, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - #379 The Unexamined Wife, Jaffe, Sherril, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - #380 Imagoes, Coleman, Wanda, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - #380 Imagoes, Coleman, Wanda, Artwork, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - #380 Imagoes, Coleman, Wanda, Manuscript, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - #380 Imagoes, Coleman, Wanda, Manuscript, First Proof, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - #380 Imagoes, Coleman, Wanda, Second Proof, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - #380 Imagoes, Coleman, Wanda, Final Proof, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - #381 Under Words, Kelly, Robert, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - #381 Under Words, Kelly, Robert, Artwork, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - #381 Under Words, Kelly, Robert, Manuscript, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - #381 Under Words, Kelly, Robert, First Proof, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - #381 Under Words, Kelly, Robert, Second Proof, Final Proof, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - #381 Under Words, Kelly, Robert, Final Proof, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - #381 Under Words, Kelly, Robert, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - #382 Hot Water Music, Bukowski, Charles, Correspondence, Notes, Review, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - #382 Hot Water Music, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - #382 Hot Water Music, Bukowski, Charles, Ephemera, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - #382 Hot Water Music, Bukowski, Charles, Manuscript, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - #382 Hot Water Music, Bukowski, Charles, First Proof, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - #382 Hot Water Music, Bukowski, Charles, Second Proof, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - #382 Hot Water Music, Bukowski, Charles, Third Proof, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - #382 Hot Water Music, Bukowski, Charles, 1 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - #382 Hot Water Music,, Bukowski, Charles, 4 Hardcover copies, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - #383 Young Robert Duncan, Faas, Ekbert, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - #383 Young Robert Duncan, Faas, Ekbert, Photographs and Notes, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - #383 Young Robert Duncan, Faas, Ekbert, Artwork, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - #383 Young Robert Duncan, Faas, Ekbert, First Manuscript (Discarded Materials), 1983 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - #383 Young Robert Duncan, Faas, Ekbert, Second Manuscript (Discarded Materials), 1983 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - #383 Young Robert Duncan, Faas, Ekbert, Author Corrections, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - #383 Young Robert Duncan, Faas, Ekbert, Author Corrections, First Proof (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - #383 Young Robert Duncan, Faas, Ekbert, First Proof (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - #383 Young Robert Duncan, Second Proof, 1983 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - #383 Young Robert Duncan, Third Proof, 1983 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - #383 Young Robert Duncan, Faas, Ekbert, Index, 1983 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - #383 Young Robert Duncan, Faas, Ekbert, Final Corrections, 1983 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - #383 Young Robert Duncan, Faas, Ekbert, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1983 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - #384 Snooty Baronet, Lewis, Wyndham, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, 1984 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - #384 Snooty Baronet, Lewis, Wyndham, Artwork, 1984 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - #384 Snooty Baronet, Lewis, Wyndham, Unedited Manuscript, 1984 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - #384 Snooty Baronet, Lewis, Wyndham, Edited Manuscript, 1984 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - #384 Snooty Baronet, Lewis, Wyndham, Second Proofs Lacking Back Matter, 1984 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - #384 Snooty Baronet, Lewis, Wyndham, Back Matter, 1984 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - #384 Snooty Baronet, Lewis, Wyndham, Third Proof, 1984 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - #384 Snooty Baronet, Lewis, Wyndham, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1984 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - #385 One for the Old Boy, Bukowski, Charles, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - #385 One for the Old Boy, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork, Manuscript, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - #385 One for the Old Boy, Bukowski, Charles, 2 Softcovers copies, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - #385 One for the Old Boy, Bukowski, Charles, 2 Hardcover copies, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - #386 There is no Business, Bukowski, Charles and Crumb, 1 Artwork, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - #386 There is no Business, Bukowski, Charles and Crumb, Ephemera (Flyer), 1984 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - #386 There is no Business, Bukowski, Charles and Crumb, Manuscript, First Proof, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - #386 There is no Business, Bukowski, Charles and Crumb, Layout Work, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - #386 There is no Business,,Bukowski, Charles and Crumb, 3 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - #387 The Name, Meltzer, David, Correspondence, Notes, Reviews, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - #387 The Name, Meltzer, David, Correspondence, Artwork, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - #387 The Name, Meltzer, David, First Manuscript (Discarded Materials), Correspondence, Artwork, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - #387 The Name, Meltzer, David, Second Manuscript, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - #387 The Name, Meltzer, David, First Proof, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - #387 The Name, Meltzer, David, Second Proof, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - #387 The Name, Meltzer, David, Second Proof, Third Proof, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - #387 The Name, Meltzer, David, 2 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1984 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - #388 The Winters of that Country, Sanford, John, Correspondence, Reviews, 1984 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - #388 The Winters of that Country, Sanford, John, Artwork, Back Matter, Second Proof, 1984 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - #388 The Winters of that Country, Sanford, John, First Manuscript (Discarded Materials, 1 of 2), 1984 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - #388 The Winters of that Country, Sanford, John,First Manuscript (Discarded Materials, 2 of 2), 1984 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - #388 The Winters of that Country, Sanford, John, Manuscript (copy 2), 1984 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - #388 The Winters of that Country, Sanford, John, First Proof, 1984 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - #388 The Winters of that Country, Sanford, John, Second Proof, 1984 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - #388 The Winters of that Country, Sanford, John, Final Proof, 1984 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - #388 The Winters of that Country, Sanford, John, 2 Hardcover copies, 1 Softcover, 1984 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - #389 Paradise Resisted, Clark, Tom, Notes, Reviews, 1984 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - #389 Paradise Resisted, Clark, Tom, Artwork, 1984 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - #389 Paradise Resisted, Clark, Tom, First Proof (authors copy), 1984 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - #389 Paradise Resisted, Clark, Tom, Second Proof (not full text), 1984 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - #389 Paradise Resisted, Clark, Tom, 3 Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover, 1984 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - #390 The Collected Greed Parts 1-13, Wakoski, Diane, Correspondence, Notes, Review, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - #390 The Collected Greed Parts 1-13, Wakoski, Diane, Artwork, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - #390 The Collected Greed Parts 1-13, Wakoski, Diane, First Manuscript (Discarded Materials), 1984 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - #390 The Collected Greed Parts 1-13, Wakoski, Diane, Final Manuscript, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - #390 The Collected Greed Parts 1-13, Wakoski, Diane, First Proof, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - #390 The Collected Greed Parts 1-13 Wakoski, Diane, 3 Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover, 1984 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - #391 Blast 3, Cooney, Seamus, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - #391 Blast 3, Cooney, Seamus, Correspondence, Permissions, 1984 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - #391 Blast 3, Cooney, Seamus, Contributors Notes, 1984 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - #391 Blast 3, Cooney, Seamus, Artwork, 1984 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - #391 Blast 3, Cooney, Seamus, Authors Corrected First Proof (pg 5-190), 1984 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - #391 Blast 3, Cooney, Seamus, Authors Corrected First Proof (pg 199-277), 1984 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - #391 Blast 3, Cooney, Seamus, Final Manuscript (1 of 3), 1984 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - #391 Blast 3, Cooney, Seamus, Final Manuscript (2 of 3), 1984 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - #391 Blast 3, Cooney, Seamus, Final Manuscript (3 of 3), 1984 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - #391 Blast 3, Cooney, Seamus, 1 Hardcover copy, 1984 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - #391 Blast 3, Cooney, Seamus, 1 Hardcover, 3 Softcover copies, 1984 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - #392 Rude Assignments, Lewis, Wyndham, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - #392 Rude Assignments, Lewis, Wyndham, Artwork, Back Matter, 1984 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - #392 Rude Assignments, Lewis, Wyndham, Manuscript, 1984 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - #392 Rude Assignments, Lewis, Wyndham, First Proof, 1984 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - #392 Rude Assignments, Lewis, Wyndham, First Proof (Back Matter), 1984 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - #392 Rude Assignments, Lewis, Wyndham, Second Proof (1 of 3), 1984 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - #392 Rude Assignments, Lewis, Wyndham, Second Proof (2 of 3), 1984 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - #392 Rude Assignments, Lewis, Wyndham, Second Proof (3 of 3), 1984 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - #392 Rude Assignments, Lewis, Wyndham, Third Proof (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - #392 Rude Assignments, Lewis, Wyndham, Third Proof (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - #392 Rude Assignments, Lewis, Wyndham, Discarded Materials, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - #392 Rude Assignments, Lewis, Wyndham, 3 Hardcover copy, 1 Softcover, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - #393 War All The Time: Poems 1981-1984, Bukowski, Charles, Correspondence (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - #393 War All The Time: Poems 1981-1984, Bukowski, Charles, Artwork (Box 136, Folder 2)